galoor.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Galoor.com

### 1\. Introduction

Thank you for visiting Galoor.com. This Privacy Policy is written to better explain how we collect and use your information. This Privacy Policy is a binding contract and you must agree to it to the same extent as our Terms of Service in order to use our services.

### 2\. Personal Information We Collect

When using our website, we may collect your name, e-mail address, profile links, profile images, and business addresses. We will not disclose any information that you provide to us except in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

### 3\. Non-Personal Information We Collect

We may collect information about you that is not personal information. When you access our website, we may collect such things as your IP address, browser, operating system, referring URL, and other general information about our visitors. This information, on its own, cannot usually be used to identify you.

### 4\. Use of Information

We may use your information:

  * To enhance or improve user experience, the Galoor site, or the Galoor service.
  * To display your profiles.
  * To do anything else you consent for us to do.

### 5\. Cookies

In order to distinguish you from other users—especially other users on the same network as you—we need to use cookies to track your specific computer. Specifically, these cookies are used to save your preferences.

We also use cookies to keep track of advertisements. Please note that we use Google AdSense to display some advertisements, which uses the DoubleClick cookie. For instructions on disabling the DoubleClick cookie, visit [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/)

For the above reasons, the enabling of cookies in your browser is obligatory when using our website.

### 6.1 Third Party Websites

We may link to third party websites from our own website. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, these third party websites or their use of your personal information. We recommend that you review their privacy policies and other agreements governing your use of their website.

### 6.2 Facebook

Users may log into their Galoor accounts using Facebook, and potentially share other social media information. Please note that we have no control whatsoever over Facebook, and that you should monitor your Facebook privacy settings separately from that of Galoor to ensure that they are satisfactory to you.

### 7\. Third Party Access to Your Information

We protect your information from being accessed by third parties. However, since we may employ outside maintenance personnel or use a third party to host our material, there are third party entities which may have custody or access to your information. Because of this, it is necessary that you permit us to give access to your information to third parties to the same extent that you authorize us to do so. For greater certainty, every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.

Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you authorize us to use Clicky, LuckyOrange, KISSMetrics, and Google Analytics for web analytics purposes, as well as any other uses that such services make available to us.

### 8\. Law Enforcement

We may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either.

### 9\. Security of Information

We take steps to protect our systems, including using vulnerability scanning and PCI DSS-compliant hosting. However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your information. It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

### 10\. Your California Privacy Rights

We are not located in California, but we may permit California residents to use our service, and therefore fully comply with California’s privacy laws. If you have any questions about your rights under this Privacy Policy, please contact us for more information.

### 11\. Amendments

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, and the amended version will be posted on our website in place of the old version. We will also include the date that the currently displayed Privacy Policy took effect to help you determine whether there have been any changes since you last used our website, and e-mail you about the change. Like our Terms of Service, you must visit this page each time you come to our website and read and agree to it if the date it was last modified is more recent than the last time you agreed to the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the new Privacy Policy, you must immediately cease using our service.

### 12\. Contact

Any inquiries about your rights under this Privacy Policy, or any other matters regarding your privacy, can be directed to [support@galoor.com](mailto:support@galoor.com) .
